제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주, 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
한여름
Midsummer
밤 9시 17분
9:17 p.m.
프랭클린 도로
Franklin Road
야, 차타고 싸돌아다니는 거
말고 뭐 할 거 없을까?
Guys, can we do something
besides cruise?
우리 오늘밤에만 저 집 앞을
세번째 지나가고 있어
That's the third time tonight
we've driven by that house.
좋은 생각이 있어
You know what we could do.
We could go skinny dipping.
홀딱 벗고 수영하러 가자
다 벗고!
Naked!
그게 바로 신의 섭리야
That's the way God intended.
말도 안돼
No way.
- 왜 안돼? 재밌을 거야
- 너희 남자들이야 재밌겠지
- Why not? It'd be fun.
- Sure, it's fun for you guys...
우리 몸매 구경할 거 아냐
얼마나 좋겠어!
'cause you get to look at us
and that's a treat.
우리는 너희 껄 구경해봤자
역겨울 뿐이라구
But we just get to look at you.
And that's nasty.
그래서, 가기 싫다는 거야?
So, you don't want to do it?
상관없어, 난 할래
I don't care, I'll do it.
너.. 앗싸, 나도
You... Okay, I'm in.
다 벗는 건 추잡해
Naked is dirty.
추잡, 추잡, 추잡
Dirty, dirty, dirty,
dirty, dirty, dirty
추잡, 추잡, 추잡
Dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty
Dirty, dirty, dirty
정말 좋은 생각이었어, 마이클
This was such
a good idea, Michael.
너무 재밌었어
This was so much fun.
맞다, 우리 옷을 몽땅 도둑맞은
것만 빼면! 이 바보야
Wait, except for the part where
our clothes got stolen, you idiot.
그건 그렇고, 페즈
문신 죽인다
By the way, Fez, nice tattoo, man.
고마워
Thank you.
이건 '요르바 린다'의 성모야
It's the Blessed Virgin
of Yorba Linda.
- 성모님 춤추는 거 보여줄까?
- 싫어!
- Do you want to see her dance?
- No!
우리 대책을 세워야 돼
Look, guys, we need a plan.
홀딱 벗은 것들 데리고
집까지 갈 수는 없단 말야
I'm not driving up to the house
with a car full of naked people.
우리 아빤 너네가 옷 입고
있어도 미워하셔
Red hates you guys
when you're dressed.
우리 집에 가도 돼
We can go to my house.
그래, 네 엄만 평소에도 주변에
벗은 남자들이 많으니까
Yeah, your mom's
used to having naked guys around.
엄만 집에 있지도 않아
이 멍청아
She's not even home,
you moron.
"탑 40" 듣자
라디오 싱글 차트 프로그램
Put on the top 40.
앉아, 페즈
거시기랑 머시기 다 보여
Sit down, Fez!
I see London, I see Besticle.
그래서 나더러 어쩌라는 거야?
What do you want me to do about it?
나도 몰라
사이에다 끼워!
I don't know. Tuck it in.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x24 Hyde Moves In
Jul 19, 1999 on FOX
폭찹이잖아?
Pork chops?
생활비를 줄이기로 했던 거 같은데
폭찹은 싼 음식이 아니잖아
I thought we agreed to stick to a budget.
Pork chops aren't cheap.
장보러 가는 길에 고양이를
차로 쳐보려고 했었는데
You know, on the way to the market
I tried to run over a cat.
그것들이 더럽게 잽싸더라구요
But they are just so darn speedy.
여보
Kitty.
공장이 곧 문을 닫을테니
우린 절약해야 돼
The plant's gonna be closing soon.
I mean, we have to watch our money.
내가 당신 설탕 다이어트
시켜 줄게요
Maybe I could put you
on the sugar diet.
- 그럼 돈이 굳을 거예요
- 설탕 다이어트?
- That'd save money.
- Sugar diet?
달콤하죠?
Sweet?
정말 완벽하군
See, that's perfect.
한 숟갈 더 줘
Give me another spoonful.
맛도 좋고 싸기까지
Tasty and cheap.
싸다고 한 건 말야..
Now, when I say cheap...
그러니까..
I mean, you know, not...
시끄러워요
Shut up.
이게 너희 집이란 말이지? / 응
- So, this is your home.
- Yep.
이꼴을 보니까 네가 하는
짓거리가 이해 된다
This explains a lot of your behavior.
왜 이래, 여기도 좋아
포먼네 지하실보다 훨 낫다고
Come on, man, this place is great.
It's better than Forman's basement.
저건 칼라 TV야, 펜치만 있으면
채널도 돌릴 수 있어
That's a color TV,
I just got new vice grips...
so now we can watch
any channel we want.
하이드, 너희 엄마 정말로
트럭 운전사랑 도망간거야?
Hyde, your mom
really just ran off with some trucker?
아냐, 포먼. 멋있어 보일려고
내가 지어낸 얘기야
No, Forman, I made it up
because it sounds so classy.
왜 트럭 운전사랑
도망가셨는데?
Why would she just run off
with some trucker?
꽃피는 봄이라
사랑이 넘쳐나나 보지
It's springtime.
Love is in the air, man.
그렇다고 널 혼자 버려두고?
Right, and she just left
you here alone?
네가 상황파악이 잘
안 되나 보구나, 범생아
Look, I realize this is hard
for you to get your head around, Opie...
그래도 좋은 면을
놓치면 안되지
but you're failing to
see the upside here.
먹을 거 있겠다, 맥주 있겠다
잔소리하는 어른 없겠다
We've got food, we've got beer,
we have zero adult supervision.
'불량놀이' 캠프에
온 걸 환영한다
Welcome to Camp
Naughty-Bad-Fun.
재키, 입을 게 없디?
Jackie, you couldn't find anything?
미안한 얘기지만, 하이드
너희 엄마 옷은 다 창녀 옷 같아
Okay, no offense, Hyde, but all
your mother's clothes are whorey.
뭐?
What?
그치만 너한텐 정말
잘 어울려, 도나
But they look great on you, Donna.
고마워, 재키
Thanks, Jackie.
마이클, 나 집에 데려다 줄래?
Michael, can you please
take me home?
저수지에서 뭔가를
옮은것 같아
Look, I think I caught something
at the reservoir.
뱀장어같은 거?
Like an eel?
그런 거 아냐, 이 바보야
나 아프단 말야
Not that, you idiot. I think I'm sick.
나 아까 뱀장어 잡았는데
I caught an eel.
그래도, 여보..
But, Midge...
왜 여성 투사들 모임을 매주
여기서 해야 되는 거야?
why do you have to have your Woman
Warrior meetings here every week?
왜냐면 다른 회원들 남편들은
허락을 안 하니까요
Because none of the other
feminists' husbands will let them.
이런 나쁜 놈들을 봤나
Boy, those bastards.
그러게요
I know.
여보, 이 모임은
내 눈을 뜨게 해줬어요
Bob, these meetings
have really opened my eyes.
이를테면, 영어가 여성에게
아주 억압적인 언어라는 거요
For example, the English language
is so oppressive to women.
왜 "우편배달부"는 있는데
"우편배달부인"은 없는 거예요?
I mean, why is it "mailman"
and not "mailwoman"?
편지는 왜 "메일"이라고 하겠어?
mail, male
Why do they even
call the mail "mail"?
"피메일"이라고 하면 안 되나?
female
Why not call it "femail"?
맞아요! 이제야 당신도
생각을 하는군요
Yes! You see, Bob,
now you're thinking.
생각은 무슨, 하도 바보같길래
웃자고 한 말이야
No, I'm not. I'm just being funny,
because it's stupid.
그래서 당신이 문제라는 거예요
Okay, then that's why
you're part of the problem.
내 마누라가 미쳤군
My wife is a maniac.
아, 미안
'미친걸'이라고 해야지?
I'm sorry, a womaniac.
죄송해요
누가 있는 줄 몰랐어요
I'm sorry. I didn't know
anyone else was in here.
- 미지 남편이시죠?
- 그럴걸요
- You must be Midge's husband.
- I guess.
미지는 정말 열렬한
여권 투사예요
She's a real gung-ho
Woman Warrior.
- 자랑스러우시겠어요?
- 그럴걸요
- You must be very proud.
- I guess.
제가 구식인지는 몰라도
Call me old fashioned...
거기 앉아서 샌드위치
드시는 걸 보니까
but when I see you
sitting there eating a sandwich...
굉장히 화가 나네요
it makes me darn tooting mad.
가족을 부양하는 남편은
I mean, I think a married man
who provides for his family...
따끈한 음식을 먹을 자격이
있다고 생각해요, 안 그래요?
deserves to come home
to a hot meal. Don't you?
멋지십니다
You're neat.
에릭, 내가 저녁먹게
씻으라고 말했을텐데?
Eric. I thought I told you
to wash up for dinner.
머리가 엉덩이에 처박혀 있느라
잘 못듣는다는 건 안다
I know it's difficult to hear
with your head up your ass.
얼른 움직여라
Get a move on.
아저씨
Red.
진정하세요
You need to relax.
분노는 영혼에 해로워요
Anger is bad for the soul.
- 너 페즈 맞지?
- 네
- It's Fez, right?
- Yes.
- 꺼져라!
- 넵!
- Get out!
- Okey-dokey.
- 얼른 와서 씻어
- 아빠, 잠깐 드릴 말씀이 있어요
- Come on. Wash up.
- Dad can I talk to you for a sec?
하이드가 저녁 먹고 가도 돼요?
Do you think
that Hyde could stay for dinner?
또? 네 친구들까지
먹여 살릴 순 없다
Eric, again?
I can't afford to feed your friends.
너도 먹여 살리기 힘들지만
법이 그래서 어쩔 수 없이 하는 거야
I can't even afford to feed you,
but the law requires me to.
쟤네 엄마가 안 계시거든요
Look, his mom's out of town.
좋다
All right.
대신 빵으로 배를 채워야 돼
But you have to fill up on bread.
그리고 너희 둘이 폭찹 하나로
나눠 먹도록 해
And the two of you
are splitting a pork chop.
- 고맙다, 친구
- 뭐, 이런 걸 가지고
- Thanks, man.
- No problem.
네 폭찹은 없는 거 알지?
So, you do know you're not getting
any of that pork chop, right?
그렇단 말이지?
Is that so?
마이클, 저리 가
나 아파
Michael, go away. I'm sick.
나 화장도 안하고 머리도 엉망이라
추하단 말야
I don't have any makeup on,
my hair is a mess, and I look hideous.
재키, 걱정마
네 모습은 신경 안써
Jackie, come on.
I don't care what you look like.
그냥 보고 싶어 온거야
I just want to see you.
왜?
Why?
넌 내 여자친구니까
Because you're my girlfriend.
그리고 선물 가져왔어
And I got you a present.
Oh.
마이클, 너무 사랑스럽다
Michael, that is so sweet.
이렇게 사랑스러운 적이 없었어
It's the sweetest thing ever.
안아 보게 해줘
Let me hold it.
고마워, 자기
Thank you, lover.
엄마, 엄마.. 엄마!
Mom.
네, 엄마가 아직 집에 안 온 걸
내가 어떻게 모를 수가 있겠어요?
Yeah, I couldn't help but notice
that you're not home yet.
그래요?
Is that right?
네, 잘 됐네요
Okay, great, yeah.
아뇨, 아뇨, 있죠..
No, no, no. You know...
엄마만 행복할 수 있다면요
whatever makes you happy.
왔냐, 포먼
Hey, Forman.
안녕
Hi.
들어와서 편하게 있어
Come on in,
make yourself at home.
맥주는 떨어졌지만
원한다면 뭘 부수는 건 괜찮아
I'm out of beer, but if you want,
you can break something.
사실, 전화기를 찍어놨었는데
벌써 저꼴이니..
Actually, I had my eye on the phone,
so...
저건 뭐야?
What's that?
크래커에다 케찹 바른거야
It's crackers with ketchup on top for...
내가 미식가잖아
you know, for zest.
글쎄, 내가 생각하기엔..
Okay, well I'm just gonna guess...
너희 엄마 안 돌아오시는구나
that Edna's not coming back.
아냐, 그냥 약간 늦어지고
있는 것 뿐이야
No, man,
she's just been delayed a little bit.
알았어
Okay.
저기에 TV 있지 않았었니?
Okay. Didn't there used to
be a TV there?
내가 전당포에 맡겼어
Yeah. I pawned it.
엄마 TV를 전당포에 맡겼다고?
안 돌아오시는 거 맞네
You pawned your mom's TV?
Hyde, she's not coming back.
그래, 안 돌아올거야, 됐냐?
Okay, she's not
coming back, all right?
그래서 너 이젠 어쩔거야?
So what're you gonna do?
집을 팔아야지
Sell the house.
빌린 집이잖아
You rent.
상황이 생각했던 것보다
심각하구나
I guess I'm in more trouble
than I thought.
이러지 마, 하이드
난 심각하단 말야
No, Hyde. No, Hyde,
I'm serious here.
- 넌 도움이 필요해, 친구
- 아냐, 포먼, 너나 그렇지
- You need help, my friend.
- No, Forman, you would need help.
난 괜찮아 질거야
I'll be fine.
잘 났다
샌드위치 갖고 왔는데
Cool. I brought you this sandwich.
좋아, 샌드위치는 받도록 하지
Fine, I'll take your sandwich.
이거 말고 다른 도움은 필요없어
After this, no more help.
하이드 엄마가 가출하고 나서
하이드가 망가지고 있어
Hyde's mom is gone
and he is going downhill.
어두운데 앉아서 크래커에 바른
케찹을 빨아먹고 있더라구
I mean, he's sitting over there
in the dark, eating ketchup off crackers.
난 주차미터기에 붙은 껌
떼서 먹어 봤어
I ate gum off a parking meter once.
친구들이랑 내기했었거든
1달러도 벌었고
But it was on a dare. I made $1.
세상엔 별 놈들이 다 있다니까
Man, there's some
suckers out there.
크래커랑 케찹은
"K"가 들어가는 단어잖아
Crackers and ketchup are "K" words.
그래서 되게 웃긴 거 같아
Which makes them naturally funny.
세상에
My God.
내 몸에 있는 세포
하나하나가 다 느껴져
I can feel, like,
all the molecules in my body.
세어 봐야지!
I'm gonna count them. One...
하나, 둘, 셋..
two...
three...
너희들 정말 너무한다
You guys disgust me.
다들 하이드는
걱정도 안되는 거야?
Doesn't anyone care about Hyde?
이런, 도망가, 스쿠비
어서 달려
My God, run, Scooby. Now. Run.
나 정말 기가 막힌 꼴 봤다?
You know what's freaking me out?
아픈데다 화장도 안한
재키를 봤어
I saw Jackie sick, without makeup.
나 머리 털나고 그렇게
소름끼치는 건 본 적이 없어
And it was
the freakiest thing I've ever seen...
in my entire, entire life.
소세지 공장 견학간 것까지
합쳐도 말야
Including the class trip
to the sausage factory.
Ay.
난 정말 소 뱃속은
다시는 보고 싶지 않아
If I never see the inside of another cow,
it will be too soon.
육포 먹을래?
Jerky?
열여덟
...eighteen...
열아홉
nineteen...
세상에서 내 손이 제일 크다!
I have the biggest hands in the world!
젠장!
Damn it! One, two...
하나..
하이드가 도움을
원치 않는 건 알지만
So his mom's gone
and I know he doesn't want any help...
옛날 그렇게 독립적이었던
서부개척자들은
but the Donner Party didn't get any help,
and then they ate each other so...
결국 서로를 잡아 먹었잖아
야, 육포 다 먹지마
Hey, don't bogart that jerky.
맞다, 부모없는 생활도
멋질거야
Yeah, no parents would be cool.
"파리 대왕"처럼 말야
Like the Lord of the Flies.
켈소, 너 그 책 끝까지
읽어 본 적은 있냐?
Kelso, did you ever finish
Lord of the Flies?
아니
광기에 휩싸인 아이들이 서로를 살해함
No.
왜?
So?
아니야
Nothing.
하이드를 어떻게 했으면 좋겠냐?
Look, what are we going to
do about Hyde?
누군가한테
말해야 될 것 같은데
I think we should tell someone.
난 재키를 어떻게 해야 되냐?
What am I gonna do about Jackie?
걜 쳐다볼 엄두가 안나
I can't even look at her.
걘 건강할 때도 짜증나는데
지금은 어떨지 상상하기도 싫어
She's unpleasant when she's healthy,
so I can only imagine how she looks like.
야, 켈소
Kelso...
재키는 내 친구야
Jackie's my friend...
넌 천박하고
and you're shallow...
게다가 애처로워
and pathetic.
게다가 또 뭔지 알아?
And you know what else?
내 손 정말 크다!
권투 글러브만 해
My hands are huge!
They're like boxing gloves.
나는 위대하다!
권투선수 알리 흉내
I am the greatest!
알았어, 챔피언
네가 뭐라고 하든..
Okay, champ, whatever you say...
- 안녕하세요, 밥
- 안녕, 밥
- Hello, Bob.
- Hi, Bob.
아니, 샤론?
Sharon.
드실래요?
Bologna?
여보, 뭐하는 거예요?
Bob, what are you doing?
아냐, 그냥 얘기하던 중이었어
Nothing. We were just talking.
'조던 아몬드'는 우리 여권론자 꺼예요
속에 아몬드가 든 축하연용 사탕
These Jordan almonds
are for the feminists.
알았어, 미안해
Yeah, sorry.
가요, 샤론. 내가 오토맨 의자에
당신 자리 맡아놨어요
등받이, 팔걸이가 없는 쿠션 의자
Come on, Sharon,
I saved you a seat on the ottoman.
아니, "오토우먼" 말이에요
I mean, "ottowoman."
볼로냐 샌드위치는 지겨워
I'm sick of bologna.
다른 샌드위치 먹고 싶어
I want a new sandwich.
에릭, 난 걔 엄마가 스티븐을 버렸을 거
같지 않구나, 걔 엄마잖니?
Eric, I'm sure she's not abandoning
Steven, she's his mother.
걔네 엄마가 정확히 뭐라고 했냐면요
"내가 니 엄마란 건 알아"
Mom, her exact words were
"I know I'm your mother...
"그치만 난 널 버릴 거야, 스티븐"
"but I'm abandoning you, Steven."
썩 듣기 좋지는 않구나
That doesn't sound very good.
안 그래요, 여보?
No, sirree. Red?
봐라, 에릭
Look, Eric.
나도 스티븐을 돕고 싶다
나도 착한 사람이야
You know I'd love to help Steven.
I'm a giver.
그렇지만 흙 파서 먹고
살 수는 없지 않느냐
But you can't squeeze blood
from a stone, son.
그래도 우리가 집에 들러서
어떤지 잠깐 볼 수는 있잖아요
You know,
we could just pop over there...
just to check up on him.
아니, 난 거기 안 갈거야
그만 해. 난 산타 클로스가 아냐
No, I'm not going over there.
That's final. I am not Santa Claus.
당신이 산타 클로스가
아닌거야 천만다행이죠
Thank God you're not
Santa Claus, Red.
애들이 당신보면 무서워서
까무라칠껄요?
You scare the hell out of children.
꺼져, 마이클
Go away, Michael.
재키, 제발?
Jackie, please?
할 말이 있어
I really need to talk to you.
사과하고 싶어
I want to apologize...
요전날 너를 보고
비명지른 거 미안해
for screaming
when I looked at you the other day.
그건 그냥..
It's just...
너 정말 끔찍해 보였어
you looked really gross.
많이 생각해 보고
깨달은 게 있어
But I've been doing a lot of thinking,
and I realized something.
뭐냐면 니가 지금 추하다고 해서
평생 추하진 않을 거란 거지
I realized
that just because you look bad now...
that doesn't mean
you're gonna look bad forever.
아랫층에서 너희 엄마를 봤는데
I mean, I just saw
your mom downstairs...
꽤 늙으셨는데도
여전히 섹시하시더라고
and even though she's pretty old,
she's really hot.
그래서 미래에 대한
희망을 갖게 됐어
And that gives me hope for the future.
오, 마이클
Oh, Michael.
마저 들어봐
Let me finish.
내가 말하고 싶은 건
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
니 엉망인 모습은
that I realized that this whole mess...
아주 일시적이라는 거야
that's just a temporary thing.
그렇지만 육체적 아름다움은
평생 지속되는 거지
But physical beauty,
that lasts forever.
너무 맞는 얘기야
That is so true.
나중에 하자. 나중에
Later, baby. Later.
알았어
Right.
그래서 사람들한테 말했죠
더 싼 걸 팔 수도 있지만
And I tell them
I can sell them the cheaper one...
장기적으로 보면
그게 돈이 더 들거라고요
but it'll wind up costing them more
in the long run.
수학적으로 말이 안 되지만
어쨌든 사람들은 구매하죠
Which is a mathematical impossibility,
but they buy it anyway.
난 자기 일에 열정적인
남자가 좋아요
I just love a man
who's passionate about his work.
이리 와 봐요
Come here.
여기 뭐가 묻었네요
You've got a little
something right there.
아, 도나, 이쪽은 샤론이란다
Oh, Donna, this is Sharon.
너희 엄마 여권론자 그룹 멤버지
이분도 남자를 싫어하셔
She's part of your mom's feminist group.
She hates men, too.
전 모임에 다시
들어가 봐야 겠어요
I should be getting back
to the meeting.
왜 그렇게 쫙 빼입으셨어요?
Why are you all dressed up?
쫙 빼입긴, 캘리포니아에선
이게 캐주얼이야
I'm not dressed up.
This is California casual.
방금 아무 일도 없었다
There's nothing going on here.
네 엄마와 나 사이는
아무렇지도 않아
Everything is fine
between your mother and me.
알았어요
Okay.
봐라, 도나, 날 고문하는 여자 말고
친절한 여자랑 말 좀 하면 안 되는 거냐?
Look, Donna,
can't a man have a conversation...
with an attentive woman
without getting the third degree?
안 되긴요, 아빠
Sure, Dad.
좋다
All right,
사과는 받아주마
apology accepted.
이제 착한 딸이 돼야지
저 안에 몰래 들어가서
Now, be a good girl
and sneak in there...
아빠한테 조던 아몬드 좀
집어다 주라
and get Daddy
some of those Jordan almonds.
안돼요, 아빠
그건 여권론자들 거예요
No, Dad, those are for the feminists.
젠장, 저것까지 물들어 버렸군
God. They got to her, too.
너..
You...
커피 테이블이 있어야 겠구나
You need a coffee table.
네, 그게 있어야
인테리어가 살겠죠
Yeah, that would really
pull the room together.
스티븐, 내가 부엌 정리를 좀
해줄려고 했었는데, 솔직히..
Steven, I was gonna...
clean your kitchen for you,
but frankly...
좀 무섭구나
I'm afraid.
뭐, 다 잘하고 사는 것 같구만
Well, it looks like he's got
everything under control.
- 난 차에 가 있을게
- 여보
- Kitty, I'll be in the car.
- Red.
스티븐, 우리 집에서 빨아줄테니
가서 옷가지를 좀 가져오너라
Steven, why don't you go
and gather some clothes...
and I'll do a load of wash for you
at our house.
고맙습니다
Cool.
이렇게 살게 둘 순 없어요
We can't let him live like this.
여보, 얜 괜찮을 거야
Kitty, he'll be fine.
한국에 비하면 여긴 행복과
즐거움으로 가득찬 지상낙원이라고
I mean, compared to Korea,
this place is Shangri-la...
wrapped in happy-fun candy.
나도 저 녀석을 돕고 싶지만
Look, you know I'd like to help him.
우린 돈이 없잖아
We don't have the money.
사회복지과에 전화해야 겠어요
I suppose we could
call social services.
그래, 이제야 알아 듣는군
Yeah, see, now that's sensible.
네, 그 사람들이
알아서 하겠죠 / 맞아
- Yeah, they'll know what to do.
- Yes.
그 사람들은 이런걸 해마다
수천건은 처리할테니까요
I mean, after all, they take
thousands of cases every year.
애들이 너무 많아서
체육관에서 키울게 틀림없어요
So many, in fact, that they have to
house them in gymnasiums.
- 여보!
- 난방도 안 되는데서요
- Kitty!
- With no heat.
XX 젠장!
Damn it!
나도 XX 놈의
산타 클로스 노릇 지겨워!
I am tired of being...
Santa Claus!
스티븐, 가서 네 XX 싸라
Steven, you get your...
together...
그리고 XX할 차에 타
and you get your ass in the...
damn car!
우리랑 가자!
We're going!
지금 당장 XX
빌어먹을!
Now...
damn it!
움직여!
Move it!
넵
Okay.
당신은 세상에서
제일 사랑스러운 남자예요
You are just the sweetest man alive.
너네 아빠가 나한테
소리를 질렀단 말야
You know, Red really
yelled at me, Forman.
그래, 익숙해 져야 될거야
Yeah, get used to that.
이건 말도 안돼
This blows, man.
난 집에 있을 땐
누구 말도 안 들었어
When I was living at home,
I didn't have to answer to anybody.
내 맘대로였단 말야
I made my own rules.
너 때문에 난 망했어, 포먼
You screwed me, Forman.
넌 상관하지 말라고 말했잖아
I told you this was
none of your business.
스티븐, 에릭
Steven. Eric.
코코아 마셔라
Here's your cocoa.
감사합니다, 아주머니
Thanks, Mrs. Forman.
고마워요, 엄마
Thanks, Mom.
나한테 안 맞은 걸
다행으로 알아
You're lucky I don't kick your ass.
너 그 쿠키 먹을 거야?
Are you gonna eat your cookies?
- 이거 끝내준다. 나도 문신할래
- 참아줘
- That's it. I gotta get a tattoo.
- Please don't.
정말 기가 막히군
That's incredible.
그치만 역겨워
But disgusting.
기가 막히면서 역겨워
That, that's incredible and disgusting.
성모님이 10 센트짜리 동전
집는 거 볼래? / 싫어!
Do you want to see
her pick up a dime? / No!
그럼 25 센트짜리는? / 싫어!
- How about a quarter?
- No!
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정 (fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24